A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 3 FA1554
Rockefeller Archive Center
China Medical Board records, RG 3
1926-1929, 1933-1936, 1938-1939, 1941-1945, 1947, 1951-1952, 1954-1957, 1959-2014
Rockefeller Archive Center
China Medical Board (U.S.)
FA1554
23.85 Cubic Feet 44 legal boxes, 7 letter document boxes, 1 half-letter box, 2 3"x5" card file box
Scope and Contents
Type of records include: Reports, publications, newspaper articles, correspondence, reprints, photographs, and memorobilia
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
These records are in three series, 1-Administrative 2-Grants and 3-Contingent Fund
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection was donated to RAC in 2011.
- Administrative, 1926-1929, 1933-1936, 1938-1939, 1941-1945, 1947, 1951-1952, 1954-1957, 1959-2014; 1; 4.54 Cubic Feet 13 containers
  - Adusei, Johanna, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees, General Correspondence, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees, General Correspondence, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees, General Correspondence, 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees, General Correspondence, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees, General Correspondence, 2002, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees, General Correspondence, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees, General Correspondence, 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees, General Correspondence, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Certificate, Change of Number of Members and Directors, 1933, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Certificate of Amendments to the Certificate of Incorporation, 1974-1975, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Certificate of Incorporation, 1951, 1928, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Certificate of Existance, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Certificate of Type, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Change of Name, 1955, 1961, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - China Medical Board Program Schools, Countries and Addresses, 1989, 2002, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - CMB Notes, 1988-1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Corporate Seal, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1935, 1942-1943, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Guidelines for New Grant Proposals, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Historical, Letters, 1926-1947, 1926, 1928, 1933-1936, 1938, 1941, 1947, 1951, 1956, 1959, 1963-1964, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Historical Statement and Memoranda, 1927-1947, 1926-1928, 1933-1934, 1936, 1938-1939, 1944-1945, 1947, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - IRS, Tax Exempt Ruling, 1929, 1957, 1960, 1964, 1968, 1973, 1982, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Accounting Department, 1970-1974, 1976-1977, 1980-1981, 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Audit, Questions as to Need for CMB to have an Audit, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Bank Accounts, Establishing Accounts for China Schools, Neuberger/Berman, 1981, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Bank Accounts, Authorizations, 1964, 1974, 1977, 1986, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), By-Laws, Amendments, 1968-1970, 1972, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 28-29)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Chauncey Belknap, 1976-1977, 1980, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Correspondence, Miscellaneous and General, 1951, 1968-1974, 1981, 1988-1989, 1991-1997, 1999-2002, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), James E. Drorbaugh, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Estimated Taxes on Investment Income, 1970, 1975, 1977, 1982, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Exchange Visitor Program, 1969-1974, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Executive Committee Matters, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Foreign Claims Committee, re: Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Foreign Service Allowance, 1963, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Minutes Corrections and Comments, 1972-1976, 1979, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), Donald Jackson, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Patrick A. Ongley, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Opinions, Hospitality/Asian Medical Shcools, 1991, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Opinions, China Medical Board (CMB) Program Schools, 1972-1973, 1976, 1979-1984, 1986, 1988-1990, 1992-1994 1996, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 42-45)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Opinions, Contingent Fund, 1954, 1972, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Opinions, Fellowships, General, 1967-1968, 1970-1974, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Opinions, Fellowship Program/IRS Ruling, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Opinions, Various and Miscellaneous, 1951, 1969-1973, 1989, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Opinions, Visiting Professors, 1952, 1954, 1969, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Personnel, China Medical Board Matter, Office, Staff, 1972, 1975-1977, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Standard Form, Authorization Resolution, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), William D. Sawyer, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Statements, Accrued Charges, 1969, 1974-1983, 1986, 1989-1990, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 54-55)
  - Legal, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler (PBW&T), Various Government Studies, re: Private Foundations, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society-New York, 1981 June 10-11 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society-New York, Tape 1, China Medical Symposium, 1981 June 10; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound, 122 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 15743)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copy available.
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society-New York, Tape 2, China Medical Council, 1981 June 10; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound, 120 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 15744)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society-New York, Tape 3, China Medical Council, 1981 June 10; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound, 112 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 15745)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society-New York, Tape 4, China Medical Symposium, 1981 June 10-11; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound, 121 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 15746)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society-New York, Tape 5, China Medical Symposium, 1981 June 11; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound, 115 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 15747)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society-New York, Tape 6, China Medical Symposium, 1981 June 11; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound, 117 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 15748)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society-New York, Tape 7, China Medical Symposium, 1981 June 11-12; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound, 122 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 15749)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society-New York, Tape 8, China Medical Symposium, 1981 June 12; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound, 122 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 15750)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society-New York, Tape 9, China Medical Symposium, 1981 June 12; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound, 68 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 15751)
  - President Council Meeting, Board and Grantees Meeting, Trustee Meeting, Hong Kong, 2000 September 11-14 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - President Council Meeting, Board and Grantees Meeting, Trustee Meeting, Hong Kong, 2000 September 11-14, To Participants (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - President Council Meeting, Board and Grantees Meeting, Trustee Meeting, Hong Kong, 2000 September 11-14, Other Quotes (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - President Council Meeting, Board and Grantees Meeting, Trustee Meeting, Hong Kong, 2000 September 11-14, Correspondence Trustee (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Registration of Charitable Trust, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Rosario-Nash, Yvonne (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Background Information, re: Vietnam, 1988-1990, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Background Information, re: Vietnam, 1988-1990, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, 1987-1988 January-October (Box 5, Folder 66-69)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Thailand, India, Hong Kong, 1989 January-February (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Korea, Hong Kong, China, 1989 March-April (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, China Trip, Unrest Situation, Letters to and From Chines and WDS, 1989 July (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Finland,, Beijing, Xi'an, Changhai, Hangzhou, Guangzhou, Changsha, Jiujiang, Hong Kong, 1989 September-October (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Hong Kong, Indonesia, Thailand, Myanmar, 1990 January-February (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Beijing, Xi'an, Guangzhou, Hong Kong, Philippines, 1990 February-March (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Xi'an, Changsha, Guangzhou, Hong Kong, Changdu, Shanghai, Zhejiang Medical University (ZMU), 1990 June-July (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Shanghai, Bangkok, Vietnam, Guangzhou, Interciencia (Veracruz), 1990 November-December (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Philippines, Indonesia, Thailand, 1990 December-1991 February (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, World Health Organization (WHO), India, Thailand, Myanmar, Guangzhou, Chengdu, Hanghou, Shanghai, Thailand, 1991, February, April (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Lao People's Democratic Republic, Vammareth Rajpho, 1991 June (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Beijing, Xi'an, Shenyong, Guangzhou, Hong Kong, 1991 July-August (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Shanghai, Beijing, PUMC 70th, Jakarta, Xi'an, 1991 September (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, San Francisco, Chengsu, Hangzhou, Washington, D.C., 1991 December-1992 January (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Bangkok, Jakarta, Surabaya, Jogjakarta, Chiang Mai, Philippines, 1992 January-February (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Beijing, Shengyang, Xi'an, Kunming, Guangzhou, Hong Kong, 1992 February-March (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Beijing, Xi'an, Hong Kong, 1992 April (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Hong Kong, Chengsu, Lhasa, Beijing, VlauBator, Jak, Vjnug Pandong, Tibet, Mongolia, Hasannudin, 1992 July-August (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Hong Kong, Guangzhou, Hangzhou, Guilin, Xi'an, Beijing, PUMC, 1992 August-September (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Beijing, Changsha, Beijing, Shanghai, 1992 October (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Sawyer, William D. (WDS), Trip Reports, Washington, D.C., Seoul (APACPH), Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Shand, June, 1993, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Translation of Wu Jieping Zhuan Biography, by Cai Xiadong, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 92-93)
  - Wu Jieping Zhuan Biography (In Chinese), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - The Yu Wang Fu Association of Peking University Medical College (PUMC), Address Directory, 1957, 1959, 1972, 1981-1982, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Trustee, J. Robert Buchanan, CMB Related Travel to China, 1998, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Trustee, Jordan Cohen, General, Curriculum Vitae (CV), Retirement, 1998-1999, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Trustee, Jordan Cohen, Trip to China, 1999 April 29-May 11, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Trustee, Don Eugene Demeter, 1996-2000, 2002, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Trustee, Don Eugene Demeter, Publications, Chinese Name, 1984, 1990-1991, 1995, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Trustee, Don Eugene Demeter, CMB Trip, PUMC 75th Leader Meeting, 1992 September 11-21 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Trustee, Walter G. Ehlers, Curriculum Vitae (CV) and Elections, 1981-1982, 1984-1987, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Trustee, Walter G. Ehlers, CMB Trips, 1983, 1985, 1987, 1992, 1994, 1998, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Trustee, Robert H. M. Ferguson, Secretary of CMB, Curriculum Vitae (CV) and Elections, 1974-1992, 1994, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Trustee, Frances M. Harrison, Treasurer, 1967, 1971-1972, 1974-1982, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Trustee, Frances M. Harrison, Treasurer, 1982, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 105A)
    Restricted-personnel material
  - Trustee, Dwight Heald Perkins, 1995, 1997-2000, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Trustee, Dwight Heald Perkins, Curriculum Vitae (CV), 1994, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Trustee, M. Roy Schwarz, 1997-2000, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Trustee, M. Roy Schwarz, Curriculum Vitae (CV), 2001 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Trustee, M. Roy Schwarz, Passport and Visa, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Trustee, Gloria H. Spivak, General, 1981-16982, 1997-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Trustee, Gloria H. Spivak, Curriculum Vitae (CV) and Elections, 1979-1987, 1989, 2002, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Trustee, Gloria H. Spivak, CMB Trips, 1981,1986, 1989-1990, 1996-1998, 2000, 2002, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Trustee, Gloria H. Spivak, Scholarship to Honor Ton That Bach, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Trustee, Gloria H. Spivak, Lawsuit, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    Restricted-personal material
  - Academic Papers, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 552)
  - Business Cards, Contact Information, and Biographical Information, 1990, 1995, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 553)
  - China Related News Clippings, 1962, 1964, 1978-1981, 1987, 1989, 1996, 1999-2005, 2007-2008, 2010-2014 (Box 50, Folder 554-555)
  - China, Trip Notes, 1982-1983, 1987, 1991-1992, 2003, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 556)
  - Correspondence, 1980, 1982, 1990, 1990-1997, 1999, 2001, 2005-2007, 2009, 2014 (Box 50, Folder 557)
  - Email Correspondence, 2001, 2003, 2006, 2008, 2013 (Box 50, Folder 558)
  - Myanmar, Trip Notes, 1990, 1995-1998, 2002, 2008-2009 (Box 50, Folder 559)
  - Myanmar, Related Notes and Memoranda, 1990, 1997-1998, 2001-2002, 2004, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 560)
  - Myanmar, Related News Clippings, 1963, 1974, 1983, 1986, 1989-1990, 1997, 2003, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 561)
  - Pamphlets and Other Momentos, 1998-2000, 200, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 562)
  - Personal Cards for Holidays and Other Special Occcasions, 1984, 1997-1999, 2001, 2003-2005 (Box 50, Folder 563)
  - Reports, Reviews, and Memoranda (Internal Business), 1979-1981, 1999-2005 (Box 50, Folder 564)
  - Speeches, 1979, 1981, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 565)
  - Thailand, Trip Notes, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 566)
  - Vietnam, Related Notes and Memoranda, 2002, 2005-2006, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 567)
  - Vietnam, Related News Clippings, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 568)
  - Photo Album, 1997-1998, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 569-571)
  - Photographs, 1997-1999, 2005, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 572)
  - Watch, China Medical Board (CMB) of New York (NY) (Box 51, Folder 573)
  - Pin, China Medical Board (CMB) of New York (NY), 2003 (Box 51, Folder 574)
  - Pin, Hanoi (Box 51, Folder 575)
  - Paper Weight, China Medical Board (CMB) of New York (NY), There are 2 identical paper weights. (Box 52)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society, NY, 1981 June 10-12, Tape 1 (Box T1, Tape 1)
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society, NY, 1981 June 10-12, Tape 2 (Box T1, Tape 2)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society, NY, 1981 June 10-12, Tape 3 (Box T1, Tape 3)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society, NY, 1981 June 10-12, Tape 4, 1981 June 10-11 (Box T1, Tape 4)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society, NY, 1981 June 10-12, Tape 5, 1981 June 11 (Box T1, Tape 5)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society, NY, 1981 June 10-12, Tape 6, 1981 June 11 (Box T1, Tape 6)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society, NY, 1981 June 10-12, Tape 7, 1981 June 12 (Box T1, Tape 7)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society, NY, 1981 June 10-12, Tape 8, 1981 June 12 (Box T1, Tape 8)
  - Medical Education in Asia, A Symposium, Asia Society, NY, 1981 June 10-12, Tape 9, 1981 June 12 (Box T1, Tape 9)
- Grants, 1952, 1972-1973, 1980-2012; 2; 18.27 Cubic Feet 38 legal document boxes and 1 letter document box
  - Asia Pacific Academic Consortium for Public Heath (APACPH), Management Advance/Chinese Participation, 92-578, 1990, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Beijing Medical University (BMU), Historical Study of Medical Exchange, 00-723, 1999-2004 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Beijing Medical University (BMU), Historical Study of Medical Exchange, 00-723, 1999-2004 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Beijing Medical University (BMU), Personality Dysfunction in Adolescents, 00-725, 2000, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Beijing Medical University (BMU), Workshop on Grant Writing, 1997 January 21-24, 92-579, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Beijing Medical University (BMU)/Association of Medical Universities & Colleges in China (AMUCC) Survey/Afflilation of USA & Chinese Institutions, 98-686, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Central South University, Brick Tea Flourosis, 01-756, 2000-2001, 2003-2006 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Central South University, Xiangya School of Medicine Domestic Violence, 01-749, 2000-2007 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing, Endowment Fund for Nursing Education, 80-395, 1980-1988, 1990-1996 (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing, Nursing Research Center Model, 99-716, 1999-2005 (Box 8, Folder 125-126)
  - China Medical Board, International Meeting on Medical Education, 96-650, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - China Medical University, 1996 President's Meeting, 1996 May 20-21, 92-579, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - China Medical University, Anesthesiology Training Center, 95-611, 1995-2004 (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - China Medical University, Emergency Medicine Training, 96-646, 1996-2005 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - China Medical University, Iodine Intake and Thyroid Diseases, 98-688, 1998-2006 (Box 9, Folder 131-132)
  - China Medical University, Lung Cancer, 00-726, 2000-2006 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - China Medical University, New Curriculum, 98-687, 1998, 2000-2006 (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - China Medical University, Psoriasis Center, 00-734, 2000-2007 (Box 9, Folder 135)
  - China Medical University, Sun Boazhi, World Federation Meeting, 92-579, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 136)
  - China Medical University, Workshop on Academic Administration, 1996 May 13-18, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 137)
  - China Ministry of Health, 1981-1982, 1984, 1987-1989, 1991-2003, 2007, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 138-139)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong, 1972-1973, 1980, 1984-1992, 1996, 1999-2000, 2007, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 140-141)
  - Chulalongkorn University, 1995, 1997-2002 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Chulalongkorn University, College of Public Health, Impact of Trade Agreement on Health, 00-732, 1999-2004 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - Chulalongkorn University, College of Public Health, Public Health Education, 99-714, 1999-2004 (Box 11, Folder 144-146)
  - Chulalongkorn University, College of Public Health, XVII International Epidemiology Association World Congress of Epidemiology, 98-686, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Co-Operative Planning Development, Medical Education Meeting,1984 February 24- March 3, 80-384, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Co-Operative Planning Development, Medical Research Meeting, 1982 November 8-12, 80-384, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Co-Operative Planning, Planning/Consortium, Thai Medical Schools, 88-503, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Hanoi Medical College, Medical Education, 93.-600, 1993-1999 (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Hanoi Medical College, Medical Education, 96-662, 1996-2005 (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - Hanoi Medical College, Medical Education, 99-917, 1999-2005 (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Hanoi School of Public Health, Institutional Development, 93-601, 1993-1999 (Box 12, Folder 154)
  - Hanoi School of Public Health, Masters of Public Health Program, 96-663, 1996-2004 (Box 12, Folder 155)
  - Hanoi School of Public Health, Workshop on Curriculum for Masters of Public Health Program, 1995 October 25-31, 92-579, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 157-158)
  - Harbin Medical University, Community Health, 99-707, 1999-2005 (Box 12, Folder 158)
  - Institute of Community Health, 1995-1996, 1998-2000, 2002, 2004, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 159)
  - Institute of Community Health, Education of Health Administrators, 95-625, 1995-2005 (Box 12, Folder 160)
  - Institute of Community Health, Education of Health Administrators, 95-625, 1995-2005 (Box 13, Folder 161)
  - Institute of Community Health, Education Infrastructure, 99-713, 1999-2004 (Box 13, Folder 162)
  - Institute of Medicine, Mandalay, Medical Education, 95-627, 1995-2007 (Box 13, Folder 163)
  - Institute of Medicine 1, Medical Information Center, 99-708, 1999-2003 (Box 13, Folder 164)
  - Institute of Medicine 2, Medical Education, 95-626, 1995-2003 (Box 13, Folder 165)
  - Institute of Medicine 2, Research Infrastructure, 99-712, 1999-2003 (Box 13, Folder 166)
  - Institute of Medicine 2, Staff Development, 99-711, 1999-2003 (Box 13, Folder 167)
  - Jiujiang Medical College, 3-Year Higher Nursing Education, 02-767, 2000-2005 (Box 13, Folder 168)
  - Jiujiang Medical College, Assist Student with Tuition, 98-686, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 169)
  - Jiujiang Medical College, Health Information Management, 01-758, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 170)
  - Jiujiang Medical College, Medical Education Reform, 98-690, 1998-2005 (Box 14, Folder 171)
  - Jiujiang Medical College, President's Council Meeting, 2001 October 29, 98-686, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 172)
  - London School of Hygiene & Tropical Medicine (LSHTM), 2008, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 173)
  - Manipal College of Medical Sciences, 1996, 1998-2003 (Box 14, Folder 174)
  - Medical Center, Fudan University, Chronic Disease, 01-757, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 175)
  - Medical Center, Fudan University (Shanghai Medical University), Molecular Medicine, 99-702, 1999-2004, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 176)
  - Medical Center, Fudan University (Shanghai Medical University), Pediatric Respiratory Diseases, 95-620, 1995, 1997-2002 (Box 14, Folder 177)
  - Medical Center, Fudan University, Smoking Prevention, 01-752, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 178)